var en_fillers = [
    {
        "Subject":"The magician",
        "Verb":"disappeared",
        "PP1":"into the box",
        "PP2":"in front of the\naudience who were\nreally impressed",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"14 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":1
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"interned",
        "PP1":"at a startup company",
        "PP2":"in San Francisco",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"9 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":2
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The athlete",
        "Verb":"ran",
        "PP1":"towards the gate",
        "PP2":"with the baton",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"11 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":3
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The astronomer",
        "Verb":"looked",
        "PP1":"into the starry sky",
        "PP2":"through the\ntelescope",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"8 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":4
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The bus driver",
        "Verb":"spent a really long\ntime",
        "PP1":"at an intersection",
        "PP2":"during rush hour",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"5 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":11,
        "Group":5
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The dog",
        "Verb":"ran",
        "PP1":"across the road",
        "PP2":"while chasing a\nrabbit",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"15 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":29,
        "Group":6
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The cat",
        "Verb":"jumped",
        "PP1":"onto the kitchen\ncounter",
        "PP2":"from the dining room\ntable",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"10 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":7
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The mouse",
        "Verb":"nibbled some cheese",
        "PP1":"in the middle of the\nnight",
        "PP2":"on the kitchen floor",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"12 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":8
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The snake",
        "Verb":"slithered",
        "PP1":"in the long grass",
        "PP2":"in the backyard",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"10 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":9
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The shark",
        "Verb":"swam",
        "PP1":"along the coral reef",
        "PP2":"off the coast",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"13 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":10
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The lion",
        "Verb":"hunted",
        "PP1":"a fast and nimble\nzebra",
        "PP2":"next to the river",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"6 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":11
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The boy",
        "Verb":"read",
        "PP1":"a fantasy book\nwritten by his\nfavorite author",
        "PP2":"in the library",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"13 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":12
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"built",
        "PP1":"a large tower",
        "PP2":"out of blocks",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"6 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":13
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The teacher",
        "Verb":"graded",
        "PP1":"all of the exams",
        "PP2":"after school",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"14 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The teacher",
        "Verb":"graded",
        "PP1":"all of the exams",
        "PP2":"after school",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"15 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27,
        "Group":15
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The policeman",
        "Verb":"questioned the\nsuspect",
        "PP1":"for several hours",
        "PP2":"at the precinct",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"11 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":16
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The firefighter",
        "Verb":"saved a cat",
        "PP1":"from a tree",
        "PP2":"with a ladder",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"10 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The carpenter",
        "Verb":"built",
        "PP1":"a dining table",
        "PP2":"out of oak",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"9 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14,
        "Group":18
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The farmer",
        "Verb":"repaired",
        "PP1":"her old tractor",
        "PP2":"by herself",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"9 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14,
        "Group":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The pilot",
        "Verb":"used the radio",
        "PP1":"to inform air\ntraffic control",
        "PP2":"about an emergency",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"11 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The shoemaker",
        "Verb":"removed",
        "PP1":"the worn sole",
        "PP2":"from the loafers",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"15 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24,
        "Group":21
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The salesperson",
        "Verb":"offered a discount",
        "PP1":"for the necklace",
        "PP2":"to his friend",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"15 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The bartender",
        "Verb":"poured a drink",
        "PP1":"from the expensive\nbottle of whiskey",
        "PP2":"into the glass",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"5 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":10,
        "Group":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The construction\nworker",
        "Verb":"reviewed the\nblueprints",
        "PP1":"for the building",
        "PP2":"with his supervisor",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"7 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":12,
        "Group":24
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The florist",
        "Verb":"arranged flowers",
        "PP1":"for the wedding",
        "PP2":"on Friday",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"9 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":25
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The custodian",
        "Verb":"placed a sign",
        "PP1":"on the wet floor",
        "PP2":"in the hallway",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"7 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":26
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The chef",
        "Verb":"stirred the pot",
        "PP1":"with a wooden ladle",
        "PP2":"to keep the food\nfrom burning",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"8 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":27
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The tour guide",
        "Verb":"talked about the\nmonument",
        "PP1":"in a loud voice",
        "PP2":"so that everyone\ncould hear",
        "Transitivity":null,
        "ModifierPosition":null,
        "ModifierLen":null,
        "Condition":"filler",
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":true,
        "math_question":"6 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":28
    }
]